[11/26~12/2: One Lucky Winner Daily for Ebike & Drone. More Details Here.](https://www.aventon.com/pages/giveaway-black-friday-2024)

——

View All Offers 7

SUPPORT

Send us a message

Have a question about something not found in our support links? Mon-Fri 9am-4:30pm PST

US/EN 

YOUR OFFERS

 _Goes to search page with current search query_

    EBIKES
    
    * Shop By Category
    * Shop By Model
    
    2 Year Warranty
    
    Free Shipping

    14-Day Returns
    
    * 
        
        eMTB Mid-Drive NEW
        
        Nowhere it can’t go.
        
    * 
        
        Commuter
        
        It's part of the job.
        
    * 
        
        Fat Tire, Off Road
        
        No roads necessary.
        
    * 
        
        Folding
        
        It fits where most can't.
        
    * 
        
        Cruise
        
        Leisure in motion.
        
    * 
        
        Step-Through
        
        Saddle up with ease.
        
    * 
        
        Cargo & Utility NEW
        
        Hauls what most won’t.
        
    * 
        
        Lightweight
        
        Grab and go.

    * 
        
        Abound NEW
        
        Cargo Ebike
        
    * 
        
        Aventure
        
        All Terrain Fat Tire Ebike
        
    * 
        
        Level
        
        Commuter Ebike
        
    * 
        
        Pace 500
        
        Cruiser+ Ebike
        
    * 
        
        Ramblas NEW
        
        Electric Mountain Bike
        
    * 
        
        Sinch
        
        Folding Fat Tire Ebike
        
    * 
        
        Soltera
        
        Lightweight City Ebike

    1,800+ Bike Shops
    
    Ebike service & test rides

    TUV Safety Certified
    
    Dedicated to your safety

    Time Magazine Award

    EQUIPMENT
    
    * Accessories
    * Components

    1,800+ Bike Shops
    
    Ebike service & test rides

    TUV Safety Certified
    
    Dedicated to your safety

    Time Magazine Award

    COMMUNITY
    
    * Join Our Community

    * [
        
        Blogs
        
        Important things for you
        
        Explore Articles >](https://www.aventon.com/blogs/aventon_bikes)
    * [
        
        Press
        
        Aventon in the Press
        
        Read the Stories >](https://www.aventon.com/pages/press)
    * [
        
        Rewards
        
        Earn points for gear
        
        Start Earning >](https://www.aventon.com/pages/rewards)
    * [
        
        Reviews
        
        Real reviews from our riders
        
        Read the Reviews >](https://www.aventon.com/pages/reviews)
    
    About Aventon
    
    Learn about the history of our company and how we have become a major playing in the ebike industry.

    SUPPORT
    
    * Support at Your Fingertips

    * [
        
        Bike Registration
        
        Helps us better serve you
        
        Register Your Bike >](https://www.aventon.com/pages/bike-registration)
    * [
        
        FAQ
        
        Your questions answered
        
        Common Questions >](https://rideaventon.zendesk.com/hc/en-us)
    * [
        
        Manuals & Guides
        
        Support articles & resources
        
        Download Here >](https://rideaventon.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/sections/28556998692507-User-Manuals)
    * [
        
        Shipping
        
        Details of your delivery
        
        View Details >](https://www.aventon.com/pages/terms-of-service#shipping)
    * [
        
        Warranty
        
        Peace of mind for you
        
        View Warranty Details >](https://www.aventon.com/pages/warranty)
    
    Send us a message
    
    Have a question about something not found in our support links? Mon-Fri 9am-4:30pm PST

Send us a message

Have a question about something not found in our support links? Mon-Fri 9am-4:30pm PST

US/EN 

Open menu

* [EBIKES](javascript:void(0))
    
    Close panel
    
    * ### Tour our Ebike Collection

    1,800+ Bike Shops
    
    Ebike service & test rides

    TUV Safety Certified
    
    Dedicated to your safety

    Time Magazine Award

    * Shop By Category
    * Shop By Model
    
    2 Year Warranty
    
    Free Shipping

    14-Day Returns
    
    * [
        
        eMTB Mid-Drive NEW
        
        Nowhere it can’t go.](https://www.aventon.com/collections/emtb)
    * [
        
        Commuter
        
        It's part of the job.](https://www.aventon.com/collections/electric-commuter-bike)
    * [
        
        Fat Tire, Off Road
        
        No roads necessary.](https://www.aventon.com/collections/fat-tire-electric-bike)
    * [
        
        Folding
        
        It fits where most can't.](https://www.aventon.com/collections/folding-electric-bike)
    * [
        
        Cruise
        
        Leisure in motion.](https://www.aventon.com/collections/electric-cruiser-bike)
    * [
        
        Step-Through
        
        Saddle up with ease.](https://www.aventon.com/collections/step-through-electric-bike)
    * [
        
        Cargo & Utility NEW
        
        Hauls what most won’t.](https://www.aventon.com/collections/cargo-ebikes)
    * [
        
        Lightweight
        
        Grab and go.](https://www.aventon.com/collections/lightweight-electric-bikes)
    
    * [
        
        Abound NEW
        
        Cargo Ebike](https://www.aventon.com/collections/ebikes?constraint=__abound)
    * [
        
        Aventure
        
        All Terrain Fat Tire Ebike](https://www.aventon.com/collections/ebikes?constraint=__aventure)
    * [
        
        Level
        
        Commuter Ebike](https://www.aventon.com/collections/ebikes?constraint=__level)
    * [
        
        Pace 500
        
        Cruiser+ Ebike](https://www.aventon.com/collections/ebikes?constraint=__pace_500)
    * [
        
        Ramblas NEW
        
        Electric Mountain Bike](https://www.aventon.com/products/ramblas-electric-mountain-bike)
    * [
        
        Sinch
        
        Folding Fat Tire Ebike](https://www.aventon.com/collections/ebikes?constraint=__sinch)
    * [
        
        Soltera
        
        Lightweight City Ebike](https://www.aventon.com/collections/ebikes?constraint=__soltera)

* [EQUIPMENT](javascript:void(0))
    
    Close panel
    
    * ### Our Equipment

    * Accessories 30% off select accessories
    * Components

* [SUPPORT](javascript:void(0))
    
    Close panel
    
    ### Support at Your Fingertips
    
    Send us a message
    
    Have a question about something not found in our support links? Mon-Fri 9am-4:30pm PST

    Call Support

    * [
        
        Bike Registration
        
        Helps us better serve you
        
        Register Your Bike >](https://www.aventon.com/pages/bike-registration)
    * [
        
        FAQ
        
        Your questions answered
        
        Common Questions >](https://rideaventon.zendesk.com/hc/en-us)
    * [
        
        Manuals & Guides
        
        Support articles & resources
        
        Download Here >](https://rideaventon.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/sections/28556998692507-User-Manuals)
    * [
        
        Shipping
        
        Details of your delivery
        
        View Details >](https://www.aventon.com/pages/terms-of-service#shipping)
    * [
        
        Warranty
        
        Peace of mind for you
        
        View Warranty Details >](https://www.aventon.com/pages/warranty)
    * [
        
        Order Cancelation
        
        Cancel your order here
        
        Learn How >](https://www.aventon.com/pages/terms-of-service#cancelations)
    * [Liquid error (snippets/anatta-header-nav line 181): invalid url input
        
        \>](https://www.aventon.com/pages/share)

Search

 _Goes to search page with current search query_

Account

Account

items in cart, view bag 0

**Aventon Privacy Policy**

Last updated: March 21, 2021

Aventon and its parents, subsidiaries, and affiliated entities (“Avant,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this Privacy Policy ( or the “Policy”).  We have created this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information as well as the rights and choices you have associated with that information in connection with our websites and the related mobile applications and services.

This Policy applies to Personal Information we collect both from you and from third parties, online and offline, during any written, electronic, and oral communications, including when you:

* interact with our website located at [https://www.aventon.com/](https://www.aventon.com/), and all corresponding webpages, software applications, or mobile applications (the “Sites”) that link to this Privacy Policy;
* interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if the advertising and applications include links to this Privacy Policy; or
* contact us for customer service or provide information via our store locations (collectively, the “Services”).

By using our Services, you consent to the collection and use of the Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not feel comfortable with any part of this Privacy Policy, you should not use or access our Services. You should also review our Terms of Service (the “Terms”), of which this Privacy Policy is a part, to understand what you are agreeing to by using our Services.

We may change this Policy so as to reflect new laws, new services or for other reasons. When we make a change, we will provide you with notice of such updates as required by applicable law, and will revise the date at the top of this Policy.  Your continued use of our Services following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy  will be considered your consent to those changes.  You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

*** Information We Collect From You**

We collect Personal Information when you interact with our Services. Personal information is any information that relates to you, identifies you personally, or could be used to identify you. The types of Personal Information we may collect about you include both information you provide to us, and information collected automatically.

**Information You Submit.** If you buy our products online, register for an online account with us, use our mobile application, sign up for updates and marketing communications from us, participate in our sweepstakes, surveys, programs or events, request specific product customizations from us, submit a product review on our website, contact us for customer service, or otherwise interact with us via our online services, we may collect the following information about you:

* **Contact Information**, which may include your name, username, postal address, email address and telephone number. We process this information to communicate with you, including about products and services you have ordered, or to send you updates about our products or services that may be of interest.
* **Order Information and Account Information**, which may include your Contact Information, payment card information, billing address, gender, nationality or residence, and the details of the products or services you have ordered, purchased, or requested from us. We process this information to create and manage your account on our website (for example to enable you to access, update and save your preferences to the account); fulfill your orders, including product customization requests.
* **Communication Information**, which you voluntarily provide to us when making inquiries to customer care, comments on our social media, product reviews on our site, survey feedback, uploading a picture, activity (including date, time and geo-location information as well as your speed and pace and perceived exertion) or your equipment usage, view others’ activities, or otherwise use the Services. 

We use this information to respond to any specific queries you may have when you contact customer care, to understand your preferences so that we can provide you with updates about our products, events, or services that may be of interest, provide you with a more tailored shopping experience, to administer sweepstakes and giveaways, or to improve our product offerings and customer experience based on your responses to a survey or product review. Please note that if you communicate with us by phone,  subject to applicable laws, we may monitor or record the call so as to maintain the integrity of your account, provide effective and timely service, and for improvement of our products.

* **Connected Devices and Apps,** which includes information from devices that you connect to our mobile application such as the Aventon ebike you are using.  
* **Giveaways or Sweepstakes Information**, which may include your Contact Information and the details of the giveaway or sweepstakes you have voluntarily entered. We process this information so that you can participate in our giveaway or sweepstakes.
* **Social Media Information**, which may include your social media interactions with us (e.g., if you “like” or “share” or “comment” on something you see on content we post on our social media accounts, usually located on third-party platforms), and any information you actively provide to us for social media marketing purposes. We process this information to interact with you through social media or email; and administer social media marketing initiatives or social media advertising campaigns.
* **Information Shared in Public Area,**  which includes the personal information you choose to share with other users when you interact in the public areas with other users, such as to provide a review of a product.  Please note such information may be viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside the Site. If you interact with other users or register through a third-party social media site, your contacts on the third-party social media site may see your name, profile, pictures and description of your activity. Similarly, other users will be able to view descriptions of your activity, communicate with you and view your profile.

**Information We Collect From You Automatically.** When you access or otherwise use our Site or Services, we may automatically collect certain personal information about you, including:

* **Usage Data**, which may include details of your visits to our Sites, including, but not limited to, traffic data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Services.
* **Device Data**, which may include information about your device and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type, and information about the type of device you are using, mobile ad identifiers, the time and length of your visit, the website that referred you to our Sites, and the subject of the ads you click or scroll over.  
* **Via Cookies and Other Web-Based Tracking Technology**, which may include information about your preferences to make your use of the Sites more productive, via the use of Cookies. (For more information on Cookies, please see Section 2.)
* **Geo-LocationData,** which may include the precise location of your device or other general location data based on GPS data, mailing address, and/or billing address (hereinafter collectively referred to as “Geo-location Data”), to customize our Services based on your location, and to provide you with other services such as notifying you of a nearby Aventon store location, or sending you push notifications or to engage in research, product development, analysis, and targeted marketing by email, push notification, online or in-app advertising.  Please note that your location may be derived from your WiFi, Bluetooth, and other device settings. You can prevent your device from sharing precise location information, including without limitation some or all of the Geo-Location Data, at any time through your device’s operating system settings.

We use this information to provide, maintain, monitor, secure, debug, personalize and optimize our online services to and for you; provide you with customer service and technical assistance; and to generally develop and improve our products and services. We also use some of the data that is automatically collected by cookies and related technologies to understand the effectiveness of our ads and social media campaigns.

**Information From Third-Party Social Media Services.**  We all you to create an account and log in to use the Service through the following Third-party Social Media Services: Google, Facebook, and Twitter. If you decide to register through or otherwise grant us access to a Third-Party Social Media Service, we may collect Personal Information that is already associated with your Third-Party Social Media Service's account, such as your name, your email address, your activities or your contact list associated with that account.

When you interact with any of our pages or our account on Third-party Social Media Services, we may collect the Personal Information that you or the platform make available to us on that page or account, including your social media account ID and/or user name associated with that social media service, your profile picture, email address, friends list or information about the people and groups you are connected to and how you interact with them, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service.  The information we obtain depends on your privacy settings on the applicable social media service; we will comply with the privacy policies of the social media platform and we will only collect and store such Personal Information that we are permitted to collect by those social media platforms. When you access our Sites through social media channels or when you connect the Services to social media services, you are authorizing us to collect, store, and use such information and content in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Use of In-Store Cameras.** We may use cameras in stores to keep employees and customers safe and to look for ways to improve our customer experience. We do not use these cameras to identify people except when necessary for security reasons.

*** Cookies And Other Tracking Technologies** 

We use cookies and other similar tracking technologies to collect additional Personal Information automatically as you interact with the Sites and to personalize your experience. Tracking technologies we may use include web beacons, tags, and scripts. 

Cookies are small web files that a website or its provider transfers to your device’s hard drive through your web browser that enables the website’s or provider’s system to recognize your browser and remember certain information. The length of time a cookie will stay on your browsing device depends on whether it is a “persistent” or “session” cookie. Session cookies will only stay on your device until you stop browsing. Persistent cookies stay on your browsing device until they expire or are deleted.  

Certain sections of our Service and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of a certain section and verifying system and server integrity).

The cookies used on our Services may be categorized as:

* Strictly Necessary Cookies, which are needed for the Site or Services to operate as reasonably expected by you.
* Functional or Preference Cookies, which remember your name or choices.
* Performance or Analytic Cookies, which collect passive information about your use of the Site or Services.
* Advertising or Targeting Cookies, which are used to make advertising messages more relevant and personalized to you based on your inferred interests.

We use first-party and third-party cookies for the following purposes to: make our Sites function properly, or to improve our Services; make login to our Sites easier (such as by remembering your user ID); recognize you when you return to our Sites;  track your interaction with the Site or Services; enhance your experience with the Site and Services; remember information you have already provided; collect information about your activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services in order to deliver content and advertising tailored to your interests; and provide a secure browsing experience during your use of our Site or Services.

**Your Cookie Choices.** Your browser may provide you with the option to refuse some or all browser cookies. You may also be able to remove cookies from your browser.  Please remember that cookies are often used to enable and improve certain functions on our website. If you choose to switch certain cookies off, it may affect the user experience. 

You can exercise your preferences in relation to cookies by taking the steps outlined below.

* _First-Party Cookies_. You can use the browser with which you are viewing a Site to enable, disable or delete cookies. To do this, follow the instructions provided by your browser (usually located within the “Help”, “Tools” or “Edit” settings). Please note, if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access secure areas of the Site. Also, if you disable cookies other parts of the Site and/or Services may not work properly. You can find more information about how to change your browser cookie settings at [allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/).
* _Third-Party Cookies_. To opt-out of third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use advertising cookies go to [aboutads.info/choices](https://optout.aboutads.info/). Once you click the link you may choose to opt-out of such advertising from all participating advertising companies or only advertising provided by specific advertising entities. For more information about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, please see [YourAdChoices](https://youradchoices.com/control).
* _Flash Cookies_. Certain features of our Services may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Site. If you do not want Flash Cookies stored on your computer, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to block Flash Cookies storage. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For more information on how You can delete Flash Cookies, please read "Where can I change the settings for disabling, or deleting local shared objects?" available at [https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html#main](https://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/end-of-life.html).  
* _Targeted Advertising_. If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers’ target-audience preferences, you can opt-out of interest-based targeting provided by participating ad servers through the Digital Advertising Alliance ([optout.aboutads.info](https://optout.aboutads.info/)) or the Network Advertising Initiative ([optout.networkadvertising.org](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1)). In addition, on your iPhone, iPad or Android mobile device, you can change your device settings to control whether you see online interest-based ads.

We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. In addition, most web browsers provide help pages relating to setting cookie preferences. More information may be found for the following browsers here:

**Do Not Track Signals.** Currently, we do not monitor or take any action with respect to Do Not Track signals or other mechanisms, which means that we collect information about your online activity both while you are using the Services and after you leave our Services.

**Analytics.** We may use third-party providers like Google Analytics to monitor and analyze the use of our Sites. Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of a Site. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Site available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). 

**Behavioral Remarketing.**  We use remarketing services to advertise to you after you have accessed or view our Services. We and our third-party vendors use cookies and non-cookie technologies to help us recognize you device and understand how you use our Service so that we can improve our Services to reflect your interests and serve you advertisements that are likely to be of more interest to You. These third-party vendors collect, store, use, process and transfer information about your activity on our Service in accordance with their Privacy Policies and to enable us to:

* measure and analyze traffic and browsing activity on our Service;
* show advertisements for our products and services to you on third-party websites or apps; and
* measure and analyze the performance of our advertising campaigns.

Some of these third-party vendors may use non-cookie technologies that may not be impacted by browser settings that block cookies. Your browser may not permit You to block such technologies. You can use the following third-party tools to decline the collection and use of information for the purpose of serving You interest-based advertising:

* The NAI's opt-out platform: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)
* The EDAA's opt-out platform [http://www.youronlinechoices.com/](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)
* The DAA's opt-out platform: [http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN)

You may opt-out of all personalized advertising by enabling privacy features on Your mobile device such as Limit Ad Tracking (iOS) and Opt Out of Ads Personalization (Android). See Your mobile device Help system for more information.

We may share information, such as hashed email addresses (if available) or other online identifiers collected on our Service with these third-party vendors. This allows our third-party vendors to recognize and deliver you ads across devices and browsers. To read more about the technologies used by these third-party vendors and their cross-device capabilities please refer to the Privacy Policy of each vendor listed below. The third-party vendors we use are:

* **Google Ads (AdWords).**  Google Ads (AdWords) remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.  You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: [http://www.google.com/settings/ads](https://adssettings.google.com/).  Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on - [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) - for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

* **Bing Ads Remarketing.**  Bing Ads remarketing service is provided by Microsoft Inc.  You can opt-out of Bing Ads interest-based ads by following their instructions: [https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads](https://about.ads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads).  You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Microsoft by visiting their Privacy Policy page: [https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/PrivacyStatement](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/PrivacyStatement)
* **Twitter.**  Twitter remarketing service is provided by Twitter Inc.  You can opt-out from Twitter's interest-based ads by following their instructions: [https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405](https://help.twitter.com/articles/20170405).  You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Twitter by visiting their Privacy Policy page: [https://twitter.com/privacy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy)
* **Facebook.**  Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.  You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: [https://www.facebook.com/help/516147308587266](https://www.facebook.com/help/516147308587266).  To opt-out from Facebook's interest-based ads, follow these instructions from Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217).  Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](https://optout.aboutads.info/), the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada [http://youradchoices.ca/](https://youradchoices.ca/) or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](https://www.youronlinechoices.com/), or opt-out using your mobile device settings.  For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook's Data Policy: [https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)
* **Pinterest.**  Pinterest remarketing service is provided by Pinterest Inc.  You can opt-out from Pinterest's interest-based ads by enabling the "Do Not Track" functionality of your web browser or by following Pinterest instructions: [http://help.pinterest.com/en/articles/personalization-and-data](https://help.pinterest.com/en/articles/personalization-and-data).  You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Pinterest by visiting their Privacy Policy page: [https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy](https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy)
* **Criteo.**  Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.criteo.com/privacy/](https://www.criteo.com/privacy/)

*** How We Use Your Personal Information**

We may use Personal Information for the following purposes:

* **To better serve you.** The Personal Information we collect helps us to better understand and serve our customers.
* **To fulfill your orders.** The Personal Information we collect allows us to fulfill your online or in-store order. 
* **To enhance our Services.** The Personal Information we collect allows us to provide programs and program benefits, verify your participation, track orders placed, respond to your inquiries, and to keep records of our interactions. 
* **To send you marketing materials and promotional offerings from us and third party partners.** The Personal Information we collect may also be used to tailor your experience on a Site or otherwise customize what you see when you visit and use the Site.
* **To provide notice of updates.** The Personal Information we collect may also be used to advise you regarding the administration of any features or functions of the Site and/or Services you have registered to use, and to provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices.
* **To record your activities.**  For example our mobile application collects information about your trips, such as the distance rode, time riding, average speed, and elevation information.
* **For research purposes.** The Personal Information we collect may also be used to conduct research and analysis and measure the effectiveness of our Services and our offline and online marketing programs. This may be from information that we combine from other sources. 
* **To administer contests, sweepstakes, promotions and surveys.** We may use your Personal Information if you enter into any contests or sweepstakes which we or a third-party vendor might advertise, or if you accept one of our promotional offers or discounts, or if you respond to a survey from us or a third party. 
* **To ensure your compliance with our Terms and other agreements.** We process your Personal Information to enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
* **To prevent, investigate, and provide notice of fraud and or unlawful or criminal activity.** We may use your Personal Information to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding possible illegal activities, suspected fraud, safety of person or property, or a violation of our policies.
* **To comply with legal process and our legal obligations.** We may use your Personal Information to respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.

*** How We Share Your Personal Information**

We may share your Personal Information in the following ways:

* **Service Providers.**  We may share your Personal Information with third party service providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Services, to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Site, or to contact you.
* **Payment Processors.**  We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we may use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).  We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your Personal Information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information. Our payment processors are listed below with links to their privacy policies.  

* Stripe.  Their privacy policy can be viewed at [https://stripe.com/us/privacy](https://stripe.com/privacy).
* PayPal. Their privacy policy can be viewed at [https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full).
* Shopify: Their privacy policy can be viewed at [https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).  
* Shop Pay: Their privacy policy can be viewed at https://shop.app/privacy. 
* Google Pay: Their privacy policy can be view at [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

* **Affiliates.**  We may share your information with our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. Affiliates include our parent company and any other subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that we control or that are under common control with us.
* **Business Partners.** We may share your information with our business partners to offer you certain products, services or promotions.
* **Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers.** We may share or disclose or otherwise transfer your Personal Information to the Company’s professional advisors such as attorneys or accountants (“Outside Professionals”), other advisors, potential transactional partners, or other third-parties in connection with the consideration, negotiation, or completion of a corporate transaction in which we are acquired by or merged with another company or we sell, liquidate, or transfer all or a portion of our assets. 

*** As Required By Law, Subpoena or Similar Government Order. We may access, preserve, share, or disclose your Personal Information if we believe doing so is required or appropriate to: (i) comply with all laws or regulations, including any of our tax reporting requirements; (ii) comply with any other law enforcement requests or legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; (iii) respond to your requests; or (iv) protect your, our, or others’ rights, property, or safety. We may be required to disclose your information to (a) taxing authorities as part of our tax reporting requirements, or (b) law enforcement authorities or other governmental agencies or via subpoena.**

* **Our Outside Professional Advisors.** We may share or disclose your Personal Information with any of our Outside Professionals to facilitate the professional advice from those Outside Professionals. 

*** Retention of Your Personal Information**

We will only retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes for which we collected it, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting obligations or to resolve disputes. While retention requirements vary by jurisdiction, information about our typical retention periods for different aspects of your personal information are described below. 

* Contact Information such as your name, email address and telephone number for marketing purposes is retained on an ongoing basis until you unsubscribe. Thereafter we will add your details to our suppression list to ensure we do not inadvertently market to you.
* Content that you post on our Site such as reviews, photographs, videos, blog posts, and other content may be kept after you close your account for audit and crime prevention purposes.
* To the extent we record our telephone calls with you, such recordings may be kept for a period of up to six years.
* Information collected via technical means such as cookies, webpage counters and other analytics tools is kept for a period of up to one year from expiry of the cookie. 

*** How We Protect Your Personal Information**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, which is why we maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect your information’s security, confidentiality and integrity. 

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. You should not share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Site like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Site.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information transmitted to Our Site. Any transmission of Personal Information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site.

*** Your Choices**

**Opting-Out of Marketing Communications.** You may choose to provide us with your email address to allow us to send free newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials to you, as well as targeted offers from third parties. You can stop receiving promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions in emails that you receive. If you decide not to receive promotional emails, we may still send you service-related communications. If you sign up to receive text messages from us that contains promotional information, you can opt-out of receiving future messages by replying “STOP.” 

Users from the EEA, the UK, Switzerland or Canada will, if required by applicable law, receive such communications only after having consented hereto. Please note that “unsubscribe” requests may not take effect immediately and may take a reasonable amount of time to receive, process and apply, during which time your information shall remain subject to this Privacy Policy. Additionally, you should be aware that any information provided to third-parties prior to your election to unsubscribe will not be retrieved or rescinded, unless required by applicable law.

**Correction**. You have the right to correct your Personal Information that you shared with us on our Site or Services. We are committed to ensuring that your Personal Information is kept accurate and up to date. However, it is up to you to update it with any changes. You are solely responsible for correcting, updating, or modifying any and all of your personal information as it appears in, and as otherwise stored by our Services. 

*** Children’s Privacy**

Our Services are not intended to be used by children under the age of 16. If you believe a child has been using our Services without the proper consent, you may contact us at the email noted in the “Contact Us” section below and we will work promptly remove the data from our system.

*** Third-Party Websites**

Please note that our Site may contain links to third-party websites, such as delivery services and social media pages. These links are intended for your convenience only. These third-party websites and services are not related to Aventon and may have separate privacy policies and data collection practices. We have no responsibility for the third-party websites or their privacy practices and encourage you to read the privacy policies of all websites you visit.

*** Notice to California Residents**

This section applies only to California residents. Under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”), “Personal Information” is any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular individual or household. Personal Information does not include publicly available information from government records, or information covered by certain sector-specific privacy laws. A “business purpose” is the use of Personal Information for the business’s operational purposes, or other notified purposes, provided the use of Personal Information is reasonably necessary and proportionate to achieve the operational purpose for which the Personal Information was collected or another operational purpose that is compatible with the context in which the Personal Information was collected.

**Categories of Information We Collect and/or Disclose for a Business Purpose.** The following table provides for the last twelve (12) months the categories of Personal Information we have collected from consumers, the categories of information we have sold, and the categories of information we have disclosed for a “business purpose.”

|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Category of Personal Information | Collected | Sold | Business Purpose Disclosure |
| Identifiers, such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers. | Yes | Yes | Yes |
| California Customer Records (see Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)), such as your address, telephone number, and (for job applicants only) your education and other information. | Yes | Yes | Yes |
| Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law, such as age, race, sex, religion national origin, and marital status. | No  | No  | No  |
| Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. | Yes | Yes | Yes |
| Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an Internet website, application, or advertisement. | Yes | Yes | Yes |
| Geolocation Data, such as the physical location of your device. | Yes | No  | No  |
| Sensory Information, audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information. | Yes | No  | No  |

For more information about the Personal Information we collect and how we collect it, please refer to Sections 1 and 2, above;  for the business purposes for which we collect your Personal Information, please refer to Section 3, above; and to review the categories of third parties with whom we may share your Personal Information, please refer to Section 4, above.

**Rights and Choices.** As a California resident, you have the rights listed below in relation to your Personal Information; however, your rights are subject to certain exceptions. For instance, we cannot disclose specific pieces of Personal Information if the disclosure would create a substantial, articulable, and unreasonable risk to the security of the Personal Information, your account with us or the security of our network systems. 

You may exercise your CCPA rights to know, access and delete by contacting us here[https://www.aventon.com/pages/contact](https://www.aventon.com/pages/contact), or by calling: (866) 300-3311.  Please note that we will need to confirm your identity and California residency to process your requests to exercise your rights to know, access, or delete your Personal Information. We cannot process your request if you do not provide us with sufficient detail to allow us to understand and respond to it.  You may designate an authorized agent to make a request to access or a request to delete on your behalf. We will respond to your authorized agent’s request if they submit proof that they are registered with the California Secretary of State to be able to act on your behalf, or submit evidence you have provided them with power of attorney pursuant to California Probate Code section 4000 to 4465. We may deny requests from authorized agents who do not submit proof that they have been authorized by you to act on their behalf, or are unable to verify their identity.

* _Right Against Discrimination_. You are entitled to exercise the rights described below free from discrimination. This means that we will not penalize you for exercising your rights by taking actions. 
* _Right to Know_. You have the right to request the following information about how we have collected and used your Personal Information during the past twelve (12) months:

* The categories of Personal Information that we have collected.
* The categories of sources from which we collected Personal Information.
* The business or commercial purpose for collecting and/or selling Personal Information.
* The categories of third parties with whom we share Personal Information.
* Whether we have disclosed your Personal Information for a business purpose, and if so, the categories of Personal Information received by each category of third party recipient.
* Whether we have sold your Personal Information, and if so, the categories of Personal Information received by each category of third party recipient.

* _Right to Access_. You have the right to request a copy of the specific Personal Information we collected about you during the twelve (12) months before your request.
* _Right to Deletion_. You have the right to request that we delete your Personal Information by contacting us at the methods described above. If required by law we will grant a deletion request, but please note that in many situations we must keep your Personal Information to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, or for another one of our business purposes.
* _Right to Opt-Out of Sales_. You have the right to opt-out of having us sell your Personal Information sold. Aventon does not directly sell your Personal Information in the conventional sense (i.e., for money). Like many websites, we share certain information, such as your IP address, device ID, click ID, or other similar online identifiers with certain third party advertising and analytics vendors to improve your user experience, to learn how you use our Site, and to help deliver interest-based ads to you. Some of those third parties may use your Personal Information for their own purposes or to provide services to other businesses. Under the CCPA, the sharing of this type of information is a “sale,” and you can opt-out of having your information shared in this way.   

If you wish to opt out of the use of your Personal Information for interest-based advertising purposes and these potential sales as defined under CCPA law, you may do so by following the instructions below.  Please note that any opt out is specific to the browser you use. You may need to opt out on every browser that you use.

Website.  You can opt out of receiving ads that are personalized as served by our Service Providers by following our instructions presented on the Service:

* The NAI's opt-out platform: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) 
* The EDAA's opt-out platform [http://www.youronlinechoices.com/](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/) 
* The DAA's opt-out platform: [http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN](https://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN)

The opt out will place a cookie on your computer that is unique to the browser you use to opt out. If you change browsers or delete the cookies saved by your browser, you will need to opt out again.

Mobile Devices. Your mobile device may give you the ability to opt out of the use of information about the apps you use in order to serve you ads that are targeted to you interests: "Opt out of Interest-Based Ads" or "Opt out of Ads Personalization" on Android devices, and "Limit Ad Tracking" on iOS devices.

**“Shine the Light” Requests.** Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please contact us here https://www.aventon.com/pages/contact. Please include the words “Shine the Light” in the subject line of the request, and state the name of our specific website with respect to which you are requesting the information, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code.

**CCPA Notice of Financial Incentive.** In certain cases, we may offer a gift card, coupon, discount, points towards a future purchase, or other financial incentive in exchange for your participation in our Loyalty Program, or for other reasons, such as in response to a survey that seeks feedback, or for providing information about your shopping behaviors.

*** _Information We Collect for the Loyalty Program_. When you create your account and opt-in to the Loyalty Program, you will be asked to provide the following information: first and last name, email address, and will be asked to create a password. Once you have created your account, you may also save your address. You may also opt to provide your data of birth to receive an extra Reward, but this is not mandatory.***** _Opt-In to Receive Rewards._ You may opt-in to receive the benefits of the Loyalty Program by signing up online or through the App. If you do not want to receive the financial incentive, you may elect to not participate. We reserve the right to change or modify the Loyalty Program at any time.** *** _Opt-Out._ You may opt-out of the Loyalty Program and delete your account by contacting us here: https://www.aventon.com/pages/contact with your request.***** International Transfers of Personal Information**

Your Personal Information may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ from those of your jurisdiction. If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Information, to United States and process it there.

We will take all the steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your Personal Information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Information will take place to an organization or a country unless there are appropriate safeguards in place as required under the applicable data protection laws, and ensuring the security of your Personal Information maintained. If you do not want your information transferred to or processed or maintained outside of the country or jurisdiction where you are located, you should not use the Site or Services.

*** Additional Notice to Individuals in the European Economic Area (EEA), the United Kingdom and Switzerland**

This Section provides additional information to individuals located in the EEA, the United Kingdom or Switzerland at the time their personal information is collected by Us. All capitalized terms in this Section have the meaning as defined in the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and/or, as applicable, the UK Data Protection Act of 2018, the UK GDPR, or the Swiss Data Protection Act (including, but not limited to “Personal Data”, “Processing”, “Controller”, “Processor”, “Data Subject”, “Consent”).  

The Controller for the Processing described in this Privacy Policy is Aventon Bikes (Avant Enterprises Inc),  1950-B S. Grove Ave., Ontario, CA 91761.

**Legal Basis of Our Processing.**  The legal basis of our Processing of your Personal Data within the scope of application of the GDPR is as follows:

* **Contract (Art. 6 (1) b GDPR)**, where we Process your purchase transactions (e.g. orders, exchanges and returns, shipping notifications) and answer your support and customer service requests as this is necessary for the performance of Our contract with you;
* **Consent (Art. 6 (1) a GDPR):**

* Unless consent is not required under applicable law, we send you promotional communication about Our products, services, offers, and events offered by Us and others, and provide news and information We think will be of interest to you only after you consent to such communication. You can withdraw your consent at any time with future effect, e.g. by clicking the unsubscribe-link in each promotional email.
* We request your explicit consent to monitor and analyze your usage of our Services and advertising to understand their effectiveness, and to personalize your experience. 
* We also request your consent to facilitate your use of various social media sharing features or other integrated tools (such as the Facebook “Like” button) which you may use as part of social media pages.

* **Compliance with Legal Obligations (Art. 6 (1) c GDPR):**

* We Process your Personal Data for compliance purposes as may be required by applicable laws or regulations or as requested by any judicial process or governmental agency (including without limitation for our tax reporting) or as may be requested e.g. under any subpoena or court order.

* **Legitimate Interests (Art. 6 (1) f GDPR):**

* To protect our financial interests or to otherwise protect ourselves against fraud or unauthorized transactions, we Process your Personal Data, e.g. we conduct credit card screenings, and perform monitoring to identify potential unauthorized users or hackers.
* To ensure you can easily find information and learn about our Services, we Process your Personal Data to allow you to participate in interactive features of our Site or our social media accounts, when you choose to do so. 
* Pursuant to our legitimate interest in providing a secure Site user experience, we Process Your Personal Data to administer our Services and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes. 
* Responding to your comments and questions is part of our legitimate business interests in providing you with our Services;
* Our legitimate interest in promoting our business is the purpose for Processing your Personal Data to facilitate any contests, sweepstakes, or promotions and process and deliver entries and rewards;
* To protect our financial interests or to otherwise protect ourselves against fraud or unauthorized transactions, we Process your Personal Data, e.g. we conduct credit card screenings, and perform monitoring to identify potential unauthorized users or hackers.
* To protect our rights and interests (e.g. protect Aventon against legal claims) we can use your data with, or otherwise distribute, share or disclose your Personal Data to any of our professional advisors such as attorneys or accountants in order to facilitate their professional advice.

**Social Media Accounts.** We maintain accounts with various social media networks. When you visit these social media networks, a variety of Data Processing operations are triggered. We use your Personal Data when you visit our profiles on these social media networks, or when you click on the like-button on one of our social media advertisements.

When you visit our profiles, your Personal Data is not only used by us but also by the social network provider, regardless of whether you have a profile in the social network or not. The individual Processing and its scope differ from provider to provider, and they are not completely transparent to us. Details about the Processing of the social network providers can be found in the relevant social media network’s Privacy Policy:

* **Facebook** by Facebook Ireland Limited, 4 Grand Canal Square, Dublin 2, Ireland: [facebook.com/about/privacy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy)
* **Instagram** by Facebook Ireland Ltd., 4 Grand Canal Square, Dublin 2 Ireland: [help.instagram.com/519522125107875](https://help.instagram.com/519522125107875)
* **Twitter** by Twitter International Company, One Cumberland Place, Fenian Street, Dublin 2, D02 AX07, Ireland, [twitter.com/en/privacy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy)
* **YouTube** by Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland: [policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-UK](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-UK)
* **Pinterest** by Pinterest Europe Ltd., Palmerston House, 2nd Floor, Fenian Street, Dublin 2, Ireland: [policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy](https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy)

The social network providers collect your usage information to provide us with usage statistics. 

**International Transfers.**  We may share your Personal Data with recipients (including our group members, service providers or business partners, as described in this Policy), located in the EEA, the UK and Switzerland; or in the United States and/or otherwise in countries outside the EEA, the UK and Switzerland which do not provide for an adequate level of data protection from an EEA, UK or Swiss law perspective. For such transfers, we will ensure that the recipients are subject to appropriate safeguards as permitted under the applicable data protection laws, e.g. by entering into appropriate data transfer agreements on the basis of EU standard contractual clauses issued by the Commission, or by reliance upon the Article 49 GDPR derogations or corresponding derogations under the UK GDPR, the UK Data Protection Act or the Swiss Data Protection Act, as applicable. A copy of the respective appropriate safeguards is available upon request.

**Your Data Protection Rights.** You have the following rights pursuant to the GDPR, where applicable, which can be exercised using the contact details listed above:

* **Right of Access**, pursuant to GDPR Article 15, to obtain from us confirmation as to whether or not Personal Data has been Processed and, if so, access to that Personal Data and additional information about the categories of Personal Data and its source, and how it has been Processed, e.g. the purpose, the categories of recipients, the planned retention period, the existence of the Data Subject’s rights;
* **Right to Rectification**, pursuant to GDPR Article 16, to request the correction of incorrect Personal Data or any incomplete Personal Data stored by us;
* **Right to Erasure**, pursuant to GDPR Article 17, to request the deletion of the Personal Data stored by us, except for the allowed continued uses permitted by the GDPR;
* **Right to Restriction**, pursuant to GDPR Article 18, to demand the restriction of the Processing of the Personal Data where one of the following applies: (i) as far as the accuracy of the Personal Data is disputed by you; (ii) the Processing of the Personal Data is unlawful, but you reject its deletion; (iii) we no longer need the Personal Data, but you require it to exercise or defend legal claims; or (iv) you have objected to the Processing in accordance with GDPR Article 21;
* **Right to Data Portability**, pursuant to GDPR Article 20, to receive your Personal Data as provided to us, in a structured, common and machine-readable format or to request the transfer to another Controller;
* **Right to Withdrawal**, pursuant to GDPR Article 7(3), you have the right to withdraw, at any time, your consent. As a result, we are no longer allowed to continue the Processing based on that consent for the future, but such withdrawal does not affect the lawfulness of the Processing based on such consent before such withdrawal; and
* **Right to Lodge a Complaint with a Supervisory Authority**, pursuant to GDPR Article 77, to complain to a Supervisory Authority (e.g. that of Your usual place of residence or work or place of the alleged infringement).

*** Additional Notice to Individual in Canada** 

This Section provides additional information to individuals located in Canada at the time their Personal Information is collected by us.  You may request details about our privacy practices, access or correct your personal information, or make a complaint by contacting us here https://www.aventon.com/pages/contact.  If you are not satisfied with Our response to your inquiry, you may contact the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada: 1-800-282-1376 (toll-free) or [priv.gc.ca](https://priv.gc.ca/).

*** Contact Us**

If you have any questions about how we maintain your personal information, or any other questions regarding your privacy or this Privacy Policy, you can  contact us:

* Via our website: https://www.aventon.com/pages/contact
* By phone: (866) 300-3311

The latest on Aventon deals & gear

Stay up-to-date on all things Aventon when they happen.

By submitting this form, you agree to receive recurring automated promotional and personalized marketing text messages (e.g. cart reminders) from Aventon at the cell number used when signing up. Consent is not a condition of any purchase. Reply HELP for help and STOP to cancel. Msg frequency varies. Msg & data rates may apply. View [Terms](https://tracking.attentivemobile.com/61213f03d38c3e769fc56199/l/ZYG3lkXoixVY0VCnj?messageId=iNfZLcNM0VOt4zmLY&rn=IielRWdtJXZCBCah5mbhhkI&re=ISbvNmLu9GduVmdhBkelRWdtJXZChkI&sc=false) & [Privacy](https://tracking.attentivemobile.com/61213f03d38c3e769fc56199/l/zZ7RwKE3bVA7OZDvV?messageId=iNfZLcNM0VOt4zmLY&rn=IielRWdtJXZCBCah5mbhhkI&re=ISbvNmLu9GduVmdhBkelRWdtJXZChkI&sc=false).

SUBSCRIBE

Footer
------

### Support

### Electric Bikes

### Community

### Company

### Support

### Electric Bikes

### Community

### Company

© 2024 [Aventon Bikes](https://www.aventon.com/). All Rights Reserved.
